Karl Warner Junior Full Stack Web Developer

https://karlwarner.devkarlwarner.dev@gmail.com07989148953

A lover of all things tech. After many late nights and gallons of coffee I have two years of full-time self funded studying behind me. I'm now ready and eager to continue my journey within a skilled team I can contribute towards and grow with

Work experience

Full stack web developer Self Employed London

Since June 2020

- Landed my first client for whom I am building an Ecommerce site using React, ApolloClient and styled-components for the front-end, Express, GraphQI & MongoDB for the back-end.
- Building projects from the ground up with experience integrating popular API's including Stripe & Google Maps
- Created server side rendered Ecommerce site using Express, RESTful end-points & GraphQI to handle requests, EJS to serve HTML, connect-mongodb-session & multer-s3 to handle image uploads to an AWS S3 bucket.
- Creating an analytics tool using Redux & ducks for state management (WIP)
- Python project using pandas data-analysis library to convert excel spreadsheets to searchable columns and rows displayed by Tkinter GUI library.
- Multiple live demos.

Please find the full details on my portfolio @ https://karlwarner.dev

Construction Project Manager WARNERS London

From June 2015 to May 2020

Duties included sourcing new opportunities, directing logistics and overseeing projects from beginning to end.

IT Technician & Skills Tutor Self-employed London

From July 2007 to May 2015

Software troubleshooting, maintenance, networking and repair service for home users.

Technical Support Analyst Mishcon De Reya Holborn, London.

From August 2006 to October 2006

Dealing promptly with 2nd & 3rd line support queries.

Interests

Accomplished musician I've played drums for 15+ years and

been in multiple bands playing various genres, I've played Ukulele for 8 years and preformed as part of a duo in many countries during my

travels.

Travelling Biker I love the freedom and adventure of

exploring on two wheels.

Core Skills

Personal Skills

- Eager and passionate about learning new things.
- A team player who enjoys collaboration.
- Highly motivated self starter with a dedicated work ethic.
- Calm and objective thinker experienced in project ownership and responsibility.

Front-end development

JavaScript ES6+, TypeScript, React, Redux, ApolloClient, HTML, CSS, styled-

components.

Back-end development

Node, Express, GraphQL, SQL, MongoDb,

Python.

UI/UX Design

Figma, Inkscape, Pinta, Gimp.

Software & practices

VSCode, Github, Linux, Unix commands, Dev-tools, Firebase, AWS S3, Heroku, Strong

IT maintenance skills, Skills tutoring,

Management experience.

Education & Certificates

Comprehensive Online Courses

Since January 2017

Node The Complete Guide Understanding TypeScript JavaScript The Complete Guide React The Complete Guide JavaScript Data Structures and Algorithms Python Learn SQL

Visual Basic 6 Programming Barnet College London

From September 2005 to July 2006

Software Development Visual Basic 6 - Designed and developed employee management software.

OCR Level 3 Certificate for IT Practitioners. Southgate College London

From September 2004 to August 2005

 $\ensuremath{\mathsf{IT}}$ systems Installation, Maintaining equipment/applications and systems testing.

GCSE's Highgate Wood Secondary School London

From September 1999 to July 2004

Double IT, Double Science, Double Math, English, English Literacy, Music,

French